<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<privacy_policy>
    <last_updated>11.11.2023</last_updated>

    <thank_you>
        Thank you for visiting <website>www.recta.website</website> (the "Website"). We respect your privacy, and this Privacy Policy outlines how we collect, use, and protect the information you provide to us.
    </thank_you>

    <information_collected>
        <item>Name</item>
        <item>Surname</item>
        <item>Company Name</item>
        <item>Phone Number</item>
        <item>Email Address</item>
    </information_collected>

    <how_we_use_information>
        The information collected is used solely for the purpose of contacting you regarding your specific request or inquiry. We will not use your information for marketing purposes unrelated to your original request.
    </how_we_use_information>

    <data_retention>
        We will retain your information only for as long as necessary to fulfill the purpose for which it was collected. Afterward, your data will be securely deleted.
    </data_retention>

    <information_security>
        We take appropriate measures to protect your personal information from unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure, or destruction.
    </information_security>

    <no_sharing_or_selling>
        We do not share your personal information with third parties, and we will not sell or disclose your information to other companies for any purpose.
    </no_sharing_or_selling>

    <your_rights>
        <right>Access the personal information we hold about you.</right>
        <right>Correct any inaccuracies in your personal information.</right>
        <right>Request Deletion of your personal information.</right>
    </your_rights>

    <contact_information>
        To exercise these rights, please contact us at <email>info@recta.website</email>.
    </contact_information>

    <changes_to_policy>
        We reserve the right to update this Privacy Policy at any time. Any changes will be effective immediately upon posting on this page.
    </changes_to_policy>

    <contact_us>
        If you have any questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact us at <email>info@recta.website</email>.
    </contact_us>

    <consent>
        By using our Website, you consent to the terms outlined in this Privacy Policy.
    </consent>
</privacy_policy>
